const quiz2data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "My father hasn't eaten anything today. He __ be very hungry.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'must' to show we are sure something is true and we have reasons for our belief."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Mobile phones ___ not be used whilst driving.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'must not' for prohibitions."
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "___ you like me to make some coffee for you?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Would", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Will", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We can use 'Would like' when we make an offer. 'Will' is wrong."
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "'Where is your brother?''He __ be at home.'",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "could", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'could', 'may' and 'might' to say that something is possible, but not certain."
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "___ you open the door for me, please? (less polite)",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Will", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Would", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'can' and 'will' as less polite ways of telling or asking someone to do something. "
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "London is a huge city. You __ easily get lost there.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "may", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "can", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'can' to make general statements about what is possible."
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "You ___ buy a new car.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'should' and 'shouldn`t' to make suggestions and give advice."
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "My brother is coughing a lot. He ___ stop smoking.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "have", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "'Must' expresses what the speaker thinks is necessary."
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "We ___ go for dinner tonight.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "could", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'could' to make positive suggestions."
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "In this area, dogs ___ be kept on a lead.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'must' to say that it is necessary to do something."
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "It's nearly seven o'clock. My parents ___ come back soon.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "could", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'should' to suggest something is true and we have reasons for our suggestion."
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "Students ___ not leave bicycles here. ",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "can", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'must' to say that something is not permitted, not allowed."
    },
   
  ]
export default quiz2data
